This programme contains strong language.
London in the 21st Century.
For the people who live here, it can be the best of times and the worst of times.
This is the story of both in one place, of two separate worlds coming together on a bend in the river at Deptford.
So that is actually a photo from the Penthouse.
Bloody hell.
Hang on, yours is that one, Mummy, isn't it, the first one?
It's that one, I think.
How incredible to have a breakfast above the city watching over everything and the lights, it must be amazing.
Five years ago, Lewisham Council decided to sell a tower block on the river to private developers Berkeley Homes.
This is where the old roof was.
All completely changing...
It's a dream, isn't it?
Its council tenants removed and its 144 flats transformed to attract a new class of resident.
Just feels lovely.
It feels like on the riverside.
I just can't believe it, just out there, Daddy, is the inner city London.
They have to believe in the fact that it is changing.
But this dream of urban living lies at the heart of the notorious Pepys council estate.
What the fuck is wrong with you?!
Stop pushing me around!
Look, you guys.
Lovely area, this, isn't it?
Mouthing off at me all the fucking time.
Who do you think you fucking are?
A place with different rules.
Let me tell you something - there is not enough fucking hit men about.
Where a new Briton is trying to make a home.
The most hassle I get is from the stairs, from the people, with the shock and horror.
A patch on the eye, big beard.
Strange, isn't it, you have this tower block in the middle and then all the way around it...
Where life is tough.
You don't want to see him when he's drinking, do you?
He still loves you, he's still thinking about you.
Where friendship can mean the difference between life and death.
If I go to buy any drugs, kick me.
You said that yesterday, didn't you?
What did you do?
You went and bought them.
You didn't kick me, did you?
Oh!
And where wealth is no guarantee of happiness.
It should be me who's crying, baba!
Love grows, it will grow.
Three years...
You can't believe this beauty!
..Two communities on one estate.
It's beginning to appear that there's more sophisticated drinkers coming in.
It's bringing a different kind of person here as well, like changing the whole feel of the place and...
Recycling areas.
Exactly.
I think it's brilliant.
It's practically south-facing, a gorgeous view.
Eastways we've got the Dome, Canary Wharf and everything back that way, more than 180 degrees that whole view, and absolutely amazing.
It's been really nice looking out at it over the years.
In a city of 7 million people, it's rare to find yourself completely alone.
I'm the last in the tower.
Lewisham have sold to Berkeley Homes.
Everyone has been moved out.
The whole of the riverside is slowly being privatised.
There are an awful lot of housing estates that do back on to the river's edge.
Those bits of the estate that touch the river's edge are all being sold off to various developers, so, as far as fairness goes, no, I don't think it's fair, really.
But it's change, isn't it?
Progress.
So they say.
The forces of change have decided that the tower's life as a council block is over with all but one of its residents now removed to inner city estates, away from the river's edge.
But Les Brookes, a professional clown, bought his flat off the council and is refusing to sell it back.
I bought the flat because I wanted to try and stay here.
In negotiations with the council over the past 18-odd months, they've been asking me to move out, sending semi-threatening letters, some more threatening than they actually are, but it's been for the last year, "Sorry we sold you the flat, we want it back now."
And... over the course of the last year, the heating has been turned off...
It's become a fight now.
These are going to be luxury apartments.
By staying here, a few years down the line, it's obvious that this property would be of value.
Thank you, darling.
Thank you very much, thank you for...
The keys to my first home.
There's speculations, I suppose, as to how this is going to affect the Pepys estate in general.
Nobody's really going to be sure until it actually happens.
This is going to be a private block.
Over there the rest of the estate isn't private, it's a council estate.
So you're putting private property right on the edge of a council estate.
Will the two mix?
I don't know.
I don't think anybody else out there really knows.
Someone's bashing the shop up.
Morning.
Oy!
Get back off.
What's going on?
Mark, it's Lawrence, I missed my appointment with you.
I fell asleep in the park and woke up with kids chucking stones at me.
Get moving, they're on their way round to nick you, now fuck off.
If I come in contact with one of these, it dies.
I'm still a little kid at heart, but who isn't?
What man isn't?
What you doing in here anyway?
You fucking don't want to do nothing, see that?
Want to have a fight?
Come and have a proper fight.
For the Pepys residents, change is only on the horizon.
But nothing stands in the way of progress and living in the past can block the path to a happy future.
30 years old.
Yep.
Falling to bits.
Arthritis in my fingers, a bad back, curvature of the spine... ..blisters and corns on my feet and going bald.
As my old foreman, Matt, used to say, "Bearing up from the mental strain of modern living."
Wayne Tapper has hit a crossroad.
Do you think I should wear this dress?
Yes.
But they pop out.
Take them clothes upstairs!
A month ago the mental strain of hitting 30 and knowing it was time to settle down proved too much.
So he walked out on his girlfriend, Kelly, and their two young children, Tiana and Tyrell.
Tyrell, listen, are you listening to me?
If I call here and find you have been a little mm-mm, you're going to get it, you understand me?
I'm hungry, man!
It's 7 o'clock.
He's come back with a promise to be the father HE never had, to his kids.
Come on, then.
I need to tart myself up a bit more.
Get my watch, it's on the telly, babe.
Get it yourself.
Please!
Things to do!
It's your bloody fault for being at the PlayStation, innit?
And on the seventh anniversary of meeting Kelly, Wayne is hoping they can make a fresh start.
Phwoar!
THEY KISS Shut up!
Seven years, man.
Yeah, you've been a right cow!
You dickhead!
Think about it.
We went from homeless, we got evicted after we had Tyrell.
How long was we in the hostel for?
Six months?
Six months.
Jumping the trains all the time.
Jumping the trains.
Do you remember?
Oh, later.
We've come a long way.
To celebrate, they have booked to eat in Canary Wharf on the other side of the river.
This is really nice.
Thanks, babes.
Business class!
"Buy, buy, buy, sell, sell, sell!"
I can't believe, this is nuts.
It is nice, isn't it?
I've seen oysters for £1.60.
"Farmed in the clear waters off the Irish coast.
"Each additional..."
EACH!
Where are you reading?
£1.60 - EACH!
"Grilled..."
I see that.
21 quid!
Give us a kiss, then.
This is going to be one anniversary to remember, babe.
Happy anniversary.
Happy anniversary, babes.
These past couple of months have made us grow up a hell of a lot, a hell of a lot.
Life is better.
We understand each other more.
You did go a bit nuts, though.
Wayne had a midlife crisis.
It was, like, "Fuck it, I've had enough."
You were a wanker because you left me to deal with it with the kids.
I know because I was like going through what I couldn't handle.
You were acting like a total idiot.
Yeah.
I was trying to do the best I could and take care of me and the kids.
I know I wasn't dealing with it, but it was something from my parents and my background, which made me run away from the situations and run away from problems, which Tyrell doesn't have to do that.
Tyrell's young, still.
That's why we've got to drill it into his head that you can be better than that.
You have to be careful how you drill things into kids' heads.
There's bringing them up a certain way and there's brainwashing them.
Yeah, but I want to brainwash them in the way that...
No, why do you want to brainwash them?
You are wrong there.
That ain't wrong.
It ain't about drumming it into the kids, it's about the way you bring them up, the way you treat them.
Drumming positivity into his head.
You don't need to drum positivity into no-one's head.
At the end of the day, there's no point in dwelling on the past.
You want me to start dwelling on the past?
I can go on for ever!
I'm not dwelling on the past.
You are!
Wayne, there is a time in your life when you need to get over things.
Yeah.
Well, get over it!
All I'm saying is, right, how I was brought up...
At the end of the day, the kids you are talking about are my kids as well.
You're going on like I'm talking badness about them.
I'm not.
You're talking about my son and drumming it into, what?
It's meant to be a family, not a cult.
No, I'm talking about...
Listen, I've had a nice meal, I'm not going to do sit here and do counselling sessions.
It's not counselling...
Well, stop.
Why do you think you stopped drinking?
Cos you turn into a prick when you drink.
Am I being a prick?
Yeah, you are.
Really, am I being a prick?
You are.
I'm being a prick.
You are not being fair.
Oh, well.
You are not being fair at all.
You should be fair.
Have a couple of drinks and you start going on like a bitch.
What do you mean, like a bitch?
You do this every time, mate.
You just don't want to listen to this conversation.
No, I don't.
That's why we get into these arguments and these fights.
I don't want to listen to it.
I'm not going to listen to it.
Sometimes I just don't understand...
You are still going.
Give it a rest!
Seven years today.
We're meant to be looking to the future, not going on about your past.
You're not the only one who had it bitchy.
Yeah, I know.
Right, so give it a rest.
When everyone tells you to let go of the past, it takes a brave soul to stand firm in the face of change.
Lewisham wanted me out so they could complete the deal with Berkeley Homes.
Thus begun the war of attrition to get me out.
As part of my service charges, I should get caretaking service, a sweep, wash the corridor, bin room and lift.
It hasn't happened in over a year.
I pay for my heating throughout the year, but it's only turned on between October and February.
I'm told it's too expensive to run just for me.
A water main that supplied Aragon Tower has broken.
It's now looking like I'm going to be without toilet, bath or hot water for over 21 days.
My mail is going astray, at one point even stopped.
I regularly post myself letters to make sure I have mail.
Things still go missing.
It's almost as if Lewisham is slowly trying to grind me down so I'll reach a deal ASAP.
Clearly there's always going to be resistance to change and that's understandable.
Berkeley Homes is part of Berkeley Group, which is one of the principal developers in London and the South-East.
It's a company with turnover of approximately £1 billion a year.
And we seek to be the urban regenerator of choice in terms of partnership with public and private bodies.
Berkeley Homes specialise in urban redevelopment and currently have 150 building projects across the South-East.
For the next two years the transformation of Aragon Tower into the Z building will be overseen from their headquarters two miles down the river.
Split-level flats, a highly innovative, '60s design.
The cladding will have to come off and the existing window system, we'll be replacing that completely.
Right.
'It's not specifically that we chose Deptford, 'Deptford had been identified as an area requiring regeneration.'
This was one of a range of regeneration opportunities that were available at that time.
We were attracted to this one because we thought the tower, although it was in need of refurbishment, was tremendously exciting.
It's in a fantastic location, the views are stunning.
In terms of the broader estate, we were impressed with the sense of community in that broader estate as well.
Deptford is certainly a part of London which has a bit of a buzz about it and it's moving in the right direction.
We don't want to try and segregate all the community from the new people we're bringing into the area, because that's the whole idea about regeneration, the new people will come in, they will be wealthy because they can afford...
Buying into the dream will require a leap of faith and it falls to the marketing department to entice people into the unknown.
..They will demand different things and they will want to live a different lifestyle, they'll want Costa Coffees, Italian restaurants and all the things that Deptford is slowly getting.
The thing about the local area is cos that's such a negative perception of that, that is the main thing we have to try and overcome.
I'll probably get Simon to do quite a lot of local area photography because that will really help.
Deptford high street is quite cool and trendy.
It won that award recently, I can't remember what it was for.
Like the best high street...
In Deptford!
We talked about the area, they may see that as a negative.
What can we use to basically enhance the area and show them that it's...?
The views has definitely got to be the main thing.
Pretty much uninterrupted, it is like a full panorama which is something you wouldn't get anywhere else.
Greenwich is quite exciting as far as eating and drinking and socialising...
We don't want to focus too much on Greenwich but it's saying these things are nearby, you can access them, without saying this is the only thing and ignoring the immediate area, but people love to think, "Where I'm going to live in the future is really up-and-coming."
They can see their property is making money and that's what gets people excited.
The day you get to take your first customers in there will be the best day ever.
It will knock their socks off!
The actual panorama that you get standing in...
Let's have a little eyeball at this one.
Did you look in this skip?
You did, didn't you?
They have to be emptied now.
Regeneration offers much to the newcomer but it's only fair that the spoils are shared.
See that thing there and other brass doings in it.
Leol Gilbert spends his days scouring the estate for scrap metal from building sites, along with his best friend, Nicky.
One of the few people I've met who you can trust.
It's rare that you meet someone that you can trust them completely sort of thing, implicitly.
That's it.
I like those sort of people.
Where did you meet him?
In a skip.
In a skip, yeah.
I wonder who that is.
Another Bob-with-a-barrow up there.
Everyone's running around nicking our metal.
We might not get lucky today.
Not a bean.
No big bits of cast iron or nothing we can purloin.
Bumped into him in a skip, up the road, got talking and then we become friends.
It is funny, innit, we can trust each other implicitly and neither of us nick off the other.
It's weird.
We clicked.
It was skips, weren't it?
But we clicked, like.
Probably loads more in here.
'Some poor bugger's got to climb in there.
'It's going to have to be me because you got in last time.'
Come to Daddy!
There's more stuff over there, though.
Metal from the skips is taken to a scrap merchant only 100 yards from Aragon Tower.
They offer cash for scrap and the yard has become a source of income for a stream of alcoholics and drug addicts who live on the estate.
Leol has depended on heroin for 25 years.
Went through a period of not getting on with me mum but that is cos she was worrying about me and moaning every time she saw me.
Then they went to this counselling session and it's changed her.
Then she started, she came back and she would say, "Well, I can't tell you what to do because you are going to go away and do what you want when I'm not there "and can't see so me worrying about it ain't going to change that."
With me dad, it's really hard to tell cos he don't show...
Apart from once when I wanted to cash in my Premium Bonds and he had the hump cos I'd spent loads of money on drugs and I looked dreadful.
Hmm.
His words were, "You're killing yourself," and that was bad.
Do you want to change?
Yeah.
Yeah, I could do a lot better... ..in every way, actually.
If Wayne was to walk out, or we were to break up and I had to do everything here on my own, as a mother, if you have got kids, you have to carry on being a mum.
Wayne's dad wasn't around, was he?
No.
Not being a bitch or nothing, but, at the end of the day, Wayne is my bloke and I take care of him as well but I cannot have no-one hold me back.
And whether some people will see that as cutting your nose off to spite your face, or whatever it is called, I see it as taking care of business.
Life is too short, I don't know what's going to happen tomorrow so I'm not going to sit around and wait for someone to sort themselves out.
The freedom of a single life or together as a family - where does a man look to find happiness?
It's the right message, the message of hope, the message of fulfilment, the message of God, the message of progression, the message of prosperity put into 21st Century language.
The churches knew Jesus was cutting edge!
Wayne spent the last month with his sister and she introduced him to the local Pentecostal church.
They have a modern approach to attracting new members and he's been invited to the Birmingham Motor Show with the male members of the congregation.
Let me borrow that mike and let them know that.
See, I can't resist a mike at the moment.
Fellas, there's a car you all need to see called a Range Stormer.
OK.
Oh, you've heard?
The gospel has travelled!
Now, possibly, we can all like take a day off Christianity and try and steal it!
No, I'm only joking, that was a joke!
...Be praying our Lord that as we journey, you will take us safely and bring us back again.
We commit ourselves into your care and everybody says...
AMEN!
I think it's important for people to come and wake up.
People often say once they plug into a dynamic ministry like the Tabernacle, once they plug into God, of course, they come alive.
Lamborghini.
Mine was the SLR Mercedes.
I've told everyone about that already.
Range Rover, I think.
Have you seen the Porsche jeep?
Women are a lot more socially interactive as far as sharing emotions, sharing innermost feelings; men, we tend to shut down a lot more, but events like this help.
It's therapeutic when you can get-together with a brother, a guy and hang out and let the boys be boys.
Excuse me, do you know what is the top speed of this?
A top speed of 208 miles an hour.
Faster than the Lamborghini then?
Wow!
Look at the boot space!
You could fit a body in there.
Go, go, go, do!
I'll see you back at the firm, yeah?
Oh...my... !
Hold on a minute.
Praise be, man.
This is absolutely...
Stonking.
..Splendiferous!
What be the price of one of these?
The basic price for this car is about £292,000.
Is that all(!)
Just underneath you have the six CD changer and just underneath there is where the solid silver tumblers would sit.
You've got all your controls here, this one is for the electric curtains which come as standard on both models for the rear.
If you wanted them fitted on the side of the doors, you can, it's an optional extra.
Can you imagine if God or Jesus was to design a car, could you imagine what it would go like?
This has to be the kind of car God would want to drive in!
Christianity is not just about materialism, it's about success, but God wants us to have material blessings as well.
When you're able to see something, if I can conceive it in my mind, then I can have a career that can get me something like this.
You can give yourself a goal.
Of course.
You enjoy coming up here today?
Definitely, I'm glad.
Men, we never talk to each other and that is the truth of the matter.
Who invited you to church?
Was it your sister?
Well, admittedly, I was going through some problems.
Right.
And I ended up going to my sister's and the day I went to my sister's, that same day, she prayed for me.
OK.
She said she prayed for me and she was talking about the church.
I thought, do you know what, it's time for me to start going.
Right.
I just felt the love, man, I felt the hope and everything.
It felt good, it made me feel good as well.
Like a new start as well.
A new beginning.
Everything in the past has gone.
Yeah.
I used to do lots of things, I used to take drugs, I used to smoke.
Everybody has a past, everybody has some kind of issues that they need dealt with, and much like the seat of this car is massaging my back right now automatically because I've just realised...
Is it?!
Yeah, it is, it's massaging my back!
God can relax you, he can make you wake up about life.
You go from existing to start living.
Yeah.
Got two kids and all that, it's about time...
At the end of the day if you love each other, if you've already spent some of your life together...
Seven years.
There you go.
Seven, that's God complete number, seven biblically is his complete number.
It's about time that some commitment went forward, a wholesome environment where the kids can be brought up.
Yeah.
Most definitely.
Give them what you maybe never had.
Definitely.
That's another thing.
Including a Bentley!
You can do it.
Dedication, as Roy Castle used to sing, dedication.
Yeah.
THEY LAUGH The road to salvation is often tough, and can mean losing the very things you love the most.
Look, there's Donna.
She's a pretty nice-looking girl.
Oh yeah.
Three months ago Leol's long-term girlfriend Donna left him, and moved out of his flat which lies directly under the gaze of Aragon Tower.
You're never ever going to forget her?
I picked her up and thrown her out before and she's always come back.
At the end of the day, you can't... there's plenty more birds out there.
Oh, of course.
You know what I mean?
Oh yeah.
There ain't many nice as Donna.
You can't keep that in your mind.
You have to move further and find someone else.
You're in love with her, so what?
When you love someone like that, you don't change.
It's hard to get out of your head, system, you think the world of her.
I'll always think of the world of her, I always did.
All you can do is go and find another bird, or girl I mean, sorry, you can't sit thinking "She'll come back to me, "will she come back to me?"
You don't know, we can't tell.
She can if she wants and she knows it.
Whatever.
I don't think she will.
Yo u can't hang around forever.
I used to have a friend that lived in Aragon Tower, they moved out.
It's only Les now.
A brave man.
It's his property at the end of the day, he bought it.
Really nice lifestyle, really fun, I want to see the girls interacting.
It will be some time before Berkeley Homes have full access to the tower.
Ooh!
Look at that.
There are dream homes being built elsewhere.
It's lovely that, isn't it?
That's fine.
Basically what's happened is she's getting ready, just lolling about on the sofa and her friend comes in, drinking champagne, very lifestyley.
Good.
The purpose of this shoot is to try and... bring alive the brochure.
We've built an exact replica of one of the apartments, we've got the exact kitchen that we're putting in.
In fact the furniture that we've got here will go into the show home in a year or so's time.
It's aspiration, trying to make people see what we are trying to create.
Because we do our sales so early, you leave an awful lot to their imagination.
So you are trying to encourage that imagination, you're trying to make them visualise living in the properties.
In the apartments brochure it will be this shot, cut here, a bit of coffee, girl standing here.
We'll take some shots of the girls drinking champagne, waiting to go out.
Here?
And then again here, "Investment in the Future", this might work being the girl on the laptop looking at her stocks and shares.
Yes.
That's really lovely.
Head slightly more around this way.
Round that way.
OK.
That's perfect.
Mmm-mm.
With all schemes, we do a lot of research into the typical buyer profiling.
Wow!
Yes!
There's 144 apartments so there's a limit to the amount of local market that you can tap into.
That's great.
Arms out.
Try and get that light behind you there.
We are good to go!
We'll be launching within the next three to four months off-plan, certainly nothing to show for, because the building is very much as you have seen in its undressed state at the moment and getting worse before it'll get better.
Yeah, perfecto!
So what we've got to do is convince people that it's a good investment.
The aspiration of this development is the water, riverside living, and in an area that is very much on the up, is very much...
Again, it's documented as to what they're doing to the Pepys estate, the regeneration.
OK, lovely.
And to be part of that from our point of view is quite exciting.
And people will buy into that.
The question is, at what stage they'll buy into it.
Excuse me.
Last one, here we go.
Perfect!
I should go and see Donna, I've got half a dozen letters for her actually.
I'm surprised she ain't been round.
She was waiting for the cheque and she ain't come back to see if it's here.
I know it's the cheque she is waiting for because there's letters from the DSS.
She will want to have drugs.
If I give her £600 she will want to buy drugs straightaway.
A visit from Donna to collect her post offers a last chance to redirect her affections.
Come in, come in, please, beautiful, you look lovely.
16 years we've been pals, yeah.
A long time.
I just don't...
I can't live with anyone, I find living with anyone is impossible, don't matter who they are.
Gentleman, no such thing as a gentleman.
Yes, there is.
You know there is.
This is what I wanted to get...
In the two years they were together, Leol and Donna spent all £30,000 of his life savings on drugs.
Looks just like you actually, innit?
Since she left him, Leol has been clean.
Stop it!
If I give Leol a 40...
Leave some of it here, I tell you what to do, let me suggest this to you.
No, you'll use it, Leol!
I won't use it.
Because I ain't got it.
Donna, I've had it here for four days.
I've lost a score already.
Listen, I'm not going to spend your money, you know I won't do that.
Keep that for me for an emergency.
No...
Give me that 20, yeah, and put 20 in for me and I'll get us one each now.
I don't want to get one each.
What do you want?
No, I ain't been using because I go out with him every day and we've been too busy.
I've been running around all day with metal in my hands and that.
I ain't had a chance to use drugs, but that's good for me, I've been doing good.
Oh, God.
She goes so fast, everything's so quick.
I ain't been using, mate.
Stop a sec.
I don't want to see you fuck all that money off in one go.
I'll give you the key to the safe, you know I've only got the one key.
You know I wouldn't spend your money.
You should know me better.
When my other cheques come make sure you look after them.
Fuck me, if you can't trust me after all this time, who can you ever trust?
This is mine and I want some so...
I've got to go.
You look gorgeous.
See you later, yeah.
Take care.
I will walk down the road with you.
See you later.
Hang on a minute.
I've got to go.
I'm late.
For what, the doctors?
Yes.
You've got ten minutes.
If I'm five minutes late, they'll make me wait till six.
I was going to say you've got 15 minutes to be late.
See you later.
Bye.
It's hurt him.
Hasn't it, really?
Go, have a talk to her.
There ain't nothing to say, is there?
Yeah.
What do you want to do, get some more metal, yeah?
Never met a bird like it, I ain't.
She's the only bird I've ever met that I would have had a kid.
He thinks the world of her.
Everyone can see that.
You've got to go for it and try and get her back.
It's no good keep talking about her.
What's your definition of romance?
I don't know.
I've never been asked that question before.
She's the best thing that's happened to you?
Definitely.
She helps sort my head out.
She's been everything to me.
She's been my girlfriend, lover, my mentor, my mother.
I shouldn't let her be my mother but...
Definitely a lover, I want to be with her... many more years to come as well, many, many more years to come.
When the time comes to prove your commitment, actions speak louder than words.
We went shopping... waiting outside the sports shops for him, thinking where is he, getting peed off with him cos he was taking ages.
He come up to me and literally pushed me on the bench and got down on one knee in front of everybody in the shopping centre.
I can't remember him saying nothing to me because I was so embarrassed...
The only thing I remember he was getting Tyrell off his back saying, "Will you leave me alone, I'm trying to propose to your mother here."
I was sitting in the corner of the sitting room and he comes in, he was gorgeous!
Oh, gross.
WAS!
And that was it.
After that, he serenaded me under the window.
I could have went through your drawers!
Where are you?
I ain't got it on yet.
I like your hair like this.
SOBBING Oh, I can't cope with this.
I was so strong when your brother got married.
It's different when it's your daughter.
I don't know why.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I can't say anything else.
Mum.
Tyrell, you cannot tell daddy.
I didn't think this day was going to come, I thought she'd given up.
Why can't we tell Daddy?
It's a surprise.
Because Daddy can't see it.
When she was born she changed my life, that's the most beautiful baby I'd ever seen.
She taught me a lesson when she says I'm going to live with a bloke, she broke my heart, because I didn't want any bloke to touch her.
That was my little baby.
Then I accepted the way she has been and accepted Wayne like a son of mine, you know.
And now she's gorgeous, she is.
Very gorgeous.
Beautiful.
Oh, shut up!
Oh, stop it...
In the pursuit of lost love, admitting defeat is never easy.
She's always loved me, she still loves me.
When you've been that close to someone it don't wear off.
It ain't like something you can discard.
I'm not in love any more, forget it.
But with the news of another boyfriend, hope fades and old habits return.
Get rid of them.
And the mood darkens with a visit from the two of them who have come to pick up her monthly benefit cheque.
Sorry?
Are you on this or not?
No, I don't touch none of it.
He only drinks.
Sorry.
You don't need to apologise for that, I think that's a wise choice.
It's a shame to see people go down that way.
It's their lives, isn't it?
I have to love you and leave you, thanks, bye-bye.
Don't let yourself go.
When I ain't got Donna at home it ain't worth being here.
You'll get her back eventually.
I don't think that's going to happen.
Says who?
You can't...
Me.
You don't - you can't say that.
Don't put yourself down.
I need the hair of the dog!
You said you were going to pack it up and you've only got worser.
That's my opinion.
I appreciate your opinion, you know I do.
I can't stop shaking, it's really bad.
You did say you were going to pack it up, didn't you?
Yeah, sorry about that.
I'm not being funny...the scrap, you know what I mean, just go and get it didn't I.
Those are the times I want to go there and get it because I'm losing out over it.
We're both losing out.
Look at yesterday, I had to push you yesterday, didn't I?
Yesterday around Silverwood Street, you sat down and fell asleep.
Did I?
Up the road you were sleeping.
You can't sleep on the road.
I must have been so tired.
Well yours is tired, but you had three goes yesterday at that stuff.
Three?
Two or three.
You're joking!
You did.
No wonder I ain't got no money left.
You were in another world, man, that's the worst I have seen you and that's saying something.
Oh yeah.
It's just temptation to you.
Can't resist it.
He's got to do it hisself, no-one is going to do it for him.
He can only be told.
Whether he listens is another story, innit?
The battle with drugs goes on.
For the last resident of Aragon Tower the fight with the council is drawing to a close.
'Scuse me!
Arrrgh!
No, stop!
In consultation with my solicitor we agreed I should hang on for a buyback price that at least approached the average for a two-bedroom in this area - £175,000 to £180,000.
Letter from Lewisham Council: "I'm prepared to recommend the council purchase your leasehold interest in Aragon Tower for the sum of £98,000"?
Perseverance can reap its rewards.
And after a year alone in the tower, the council have had no choice but to agree to Les's demands.
I've come out good at the end of a long, hard fight.
Mixed feelings now because this is finally it, I'm moving.
I've written in my diary for Monday, "start of a new life - question mark."
It's pointless getting angry because in the long run it's not going to do me any good.
This area will be redeveloped quickly now Berkeley Homes have got their foot on this corner.
I'm calling from Berkeley Homes.
A little while ago you expressed an interest in the Aragon Tower, or the Z building, and whether you are interested in coming to our prelaunch on - you are, excellent.
I hope they all apply to these and send them all back.
770 applicants is quite a good number.
Blimey, imagine 350 people at the launch.
Oh my God!
That is amazing.
I baptise you in the name of the Lord Jesus Christ for the remission of your sins.
In the end it will get the better of you, it's only a matter of time.
How I feel about someone is not your fuckin' business, it's mine.
This is like somewhere where somebody don't live.
Thank you.
I think this is the in-place to be.
Not only that, living by the river.
I think you should go for it.